(Bernadette:)...getting our hair cornrowed
in Venice Beach. L've suffered enough.
l could take it down and put it up when
she comes over, but it's kind of heavy.
(Bernadette:)Too bad you're not as strong
as the dude in the painting.
(Raj:)Would you look at this?
l paid $25 to some kid on eBay
for a handcrafted Harry Potter wand.
(Raj:)He sent me a stick.
(Raj:)He went into his backyard,
he picked up a stick.
It's numbered. Heh.
(Raj:)Ooh. Limited edition. Nice.
- Oh, that'll be Kripke.
- What's he doing here?
(Sheldon:)We're going to work
this office situation out like gentlemen.
(Sheldon:)And if that doesn't work,
I'm going to poison his tea.
(Kripke:)- Cooper.
- Kripke. Come in.
(Sheldon:)I'm making tea. Would you like a cup?
Am I wearing a summer frock?
No, I don't want tea.
Let's get down to brass tacks.